oh good morning
what's up happy happy for the job
everybody
you all know that I love America
America's great this is one of those
periscope that's gonna get deleted
quickly but yeah what did I want to talk
about today nothing
I got nothing to talk about yeah well
good thing come on Tay I'm actually
finished with the mati the secrets mmm
we're not ready to reveal any secrets
yet Wow we have 62 people in here Oh
nope we're not gonna reveal any secrets
on this periscope we can look at the
airports though whoo air Potts oh yeah
they put one in that's nice oh yeah look
at that air product but what do we want
to talk oh we want to talk about the
latest in height wave AI let's talk
about
the first example of reinforcement
learning on board an autonomous car let
me tell you why this is hype because
nobody doubted that this would work
right they drove down this same stretch
of road multiple times and then
eventually reinforcement learning
learned how to drive the car hi oh we
could talk about cachet i - anthony
levin Donsky is back at it building
trucks I mean it's a nice picture I
guess no it's not what I did
I wouldn't use reinforcement
reinforcement learning is largely a scam
it doesn't really work that well part of
the problem is your rewards a super
sparse and to try to learn a real policy
so we're gonna do something similar the
long-term plan of kamma AI you'll see I
mean it's one of the secrets alright so
we have some great secrets we're gonna
reveal during the press know
reinforcement learning is very not data
efficient and it doesn't it doesn't
scale like what are you gonna do you're
gonna put this policy on all the cars
you're gonna you're really gonna run the
gradient on the car I don't think you
can do that you have to do it in one
place
alright guys you want to show off one
secret well what press out let's find
out both good ones you got good ones I
got the best press now I'll show you
guys one secret there's a secret shoot a
secret all part of open pound 0.5 you
guys you know 0.5 is not gonna have ways
and it's not gonna have Spotify happy
4th of July
absolutely it's a great day today is a
wonderful day today we want our
independence and our freedom from the
tyrannical British
alright guys I don't have that much to
say this morning mark that's right
check out my come a share this is
self-driving awareness to a shirt these
are extremely rare it's exciting
Spotify anyways are gone that's right
don't drink and drive kids good morning
Anthony levity is back to making trucks
maybe in China where the long arm of
Google can't reach them the beanies are
ultra rare much that is true they are
more rare
if you bought a beanie you got great
stuff what is 0.5 outs coming out not
this Friday but the Friday after um so
there are three secrets that are gonna
be revealed at press one secret is
already known by a few of you one secret
the second secret maybe you can guess
and the third secret is findable on the
Internet
so if you know the right place to look
you can find the third secret first
person to find the third secret what
should we give you what should we give
you if you find the third secret you
know one of the secrets okay okay and
CPF is a recon check out this beautiful
panda in a box look at this box I'm sure
to go to shop.com at AI and buy things
today is the 4th of July it's a great
day to buy things yeah I mean that is
true if you find the secret you get did
you get to be the guy in slack who told
everybody else
the secret yeah the secret look at it
it's a panda this has nothing to do with
the secret of course
but there's a great secret if you know
how to look but that's it that's mostly
what I wanted to talk about today I
almost forgot questions do we have
questions are there any questions
good I hate questions yeah the Volvo's
sold we sold over 150 dollars in Vegas
bro now we're not going downstairs to
the 3d printers let's talk about how to
talk about Eddie yeah I'm going on a
boat tonight I think Oh what is press
release oh not this Friday but next
Friday next Friday we'll be doing a
press release oh also I know I on
it a lot but what do you all think of
Python 3 open pilot is gonna be Python 3
compatible so we can start doing some
static type checking all very exciting
static type checking all faults on
infrastructure for data labeling maybe
that's related to one of the secrets
Tom's yeah I've been coding if you've
been watching me do my my twitches I've
been doing them in Python 3 oh yeah I'm
not gonna die because I'm putting new
hardware it now I can show you a little
see what you want to go down there we'll
go down there and then that's where I'll
leave you are the things printing maybe
they're printing hey NIC we pretty the
new hardware oh yeah Skokie's want to
say oh yeah we're free
can't show you what's in any of the
printers because of course it's secret
oh yeah pretty wide ones pretty
it is printing secret so we can't show
it to you now just kidding guys we're
printing onto the giraffes around
flippin eons ollie on shipping now are
flipped i'll show them the top of
connectors yeah they're made on the form
too so this is a special 3d printer it
gets its own room no no the work today
no one has to come to work any day
except for Mondays when we have the
meeting it's very important to come to
work on the Monday meeting very
important all right I think that's the
periscope you guys saw the 3d printers
that's all we can really ask for the
biggest thing that we're talking about
you know the driver won't be bored when
they're being monitored by driver
monitoring that's it guys the biggest
thing that we're really hyped about in
the press is hiring we're trying to hire
five people I know I did like ten but
it's five people
let's get user or you can put the new
user I just add some to it all
right